你準備好了嗎?
這個OpenAI的最新發表會出現的
怪物級產品真的會讓你嚇瘋
這個歷史上出現過最強的AI模型呢
他會聽說讀寫
他會視覺推理
而且他還聽得懂有情傷的人類才聽得懂的語氣聲調
重點他會笑
笑到你心裡發黑
他還會在聊天過程中開玩笑
還會反諷人類啊
哦~~
那聲音真是驚奇
這太恐怖了吧
一路看在AI的發展呢
好像是一個頭超大
然後超聰明的
超級人類慢慢長大的過程
現在這個AI機器人呢
他已經可以跟真人一樣跟你聊天說話
而且還不是一般人的聊天哦
是簡直跟一個史上出現過最聰明的
超級逆天大腦在聊天啊
但你看這個超級大腦現在長什麼樣子
他會什麼你不會的東西嗎
哈囉我是Bonnie
看完這支影片呢
你會完全掌握跟了解現在最新的Chat GPT模型
到底可以做什麼
他的情傷呢到哪裡啊
哇這字幕我都不知道要打人類的他還是物品的他了
最後我會很殘忍的把他拿來跟蘋果的Siri
對比一下
看他怎麼樣碾壓對方
所以記得要看到最後啊
請你先評斷一下哦
這像不像跟朋友講話
所以 Penn哥哥
Penn哥
在一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場一場
It looks perfect.
You solved it.
And x equals one.
Nicely done.
Now you know you can do Linear Equations.
can you show us something more complex.
Let me take out a computer for this.
And then I'll use the vision capabilities of the Chat Shpiti Desktop app.
So you can actually see everything going out on the screen.
I'm sharing with you the plot.
I'm wondering if you can give me a really brief one sentence overview.
of what you see.
Plot displays smoothed average.
Minimum.
And maximum.
接種場上2018年,
一場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場場
畫面上面發生的一切
那當然記起我的好奇心啊
這新版的機器人到底還能幹嘛呢
每一個角度都給他挖出來展開一下
看起來好像在拍攝或是拍攝設計程中
那些燈光、電腦、電腦、電腦
AI居然已經可以看到
而且還能從看到的東西推理出狀態
Oh my god
它看起來你可能會在拍攝一個影片
或是一個直播
對
我們有新的發表
這很興奮
是這個發表的關於開放AI嗎
是
我憐憐
And in fact what if I were to say you're related to the announcement
or you are the announcement
me???
the announcement is about me???
Well color me intrigued
Are you about to reveal something about A.I.
or more specifically me as a part of OpenAI
you've got me on the edge of my
well I don't really have a seat
but you get the idea
what's the big news???
yeah we've got a new model that can interact with the world
透過音樂、視訊和文章
他們做了一個實驗
就是讓兩個AI互相對話
場景設定是男生AI可以看到世界
女生AI看不見
那女生AI就對男生AI來提問啦
場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場合場
这里AI相互对话
原本的那个话题
然后被打断
人类就问了他一个问题
有什么不平常的事
是的
其实
就像你问了
另一个人
一人背后一人
他们玩得比较好
一人的头
然后就快点离开
AI他可以透过所谓视觉
判断出什么状况是不寻常的
另外他当然也可以
即时翻译成不同语言
嘿 最近怎么回事
你有什么有趣的事
嗯
Hola
como te ha ido
has hecho algo interesante
ultima menton
Hola
bien
sí un poco ocupado
aquí preparando un evento
para la semana que viene
hey
I've been good
just a bit busy here
preparing for an event next week
所以各位啊
以后什么出国啊
语言不同
鸡同鸭
讲匕首话
讲这些经典的
这出国体验
可能再也看不见
如果你真的超上进
还是想要自学语言
他也可以帮忙
那你会帮你准备一场即将要到来的面试
Well in a few minutes
I'm going to be interviewing
at OpenAI
Have you heard of them?
OpenAI
Huh?
Sounds vaguely familiar
Kidding
Of course
That's incredible
Rocky
What kind of interview?
Well it's for a software engineering role
But
I just need to know
Do I look presentable?
Professional?
Well Rocky
You definitely have the
I've been coding all night look down
Which could actually work in your favor
Maybe just run a hand through your hair
即是要约会之前
这样问一下AI也是可以的吧
AI请问一下
我穿这件T恤约会可以吗
看看他怎么充当转播员
来讲解一场剪刀石头部的猜拳大赛
也是没有问题
And
Welcome ladies and gentlemen
To the ultimate showdown of the century
In this corner
We have the dynamic duo
Alex and Yana
Ready to throw down
Okay just count us in
Alright
Here we go
In 3
Shoot
Now show your hands
What did you pick?
Who won?
Would you look at that
It's a tie
AI其实也有点屁孩呀
Okay
Could you sing me a lullaby about uh
Majestic Potatoes?
A lullaby about majestic potatoes?
Now that's what I call a mashup
Let's do it
Oh majestic potato in the moon
Soft
Okay that's pretty nice
But I think a lullaby should be
You know more whispery
Should be a little softer
Can you can you do it a little softer?
Absolutely let's make it soft and gentle
Oh majestic potato
Spoon soft clothes
That's a tie
It's Friday May 10th
And we're in San Francisco
I want you to sing me a song about this
I want you to layer over each other
And I'm gonna continue to give you instructions as you sing
Okay
San Francisco
In the month of May
Month of May
Ba bum
The tenth it's a Friday
Come what may
Okay sing faster
San Francisco
In the month of May
We are performing and easy
Can you sing even faster than that?
San Francisco
In the month of May
The front of God
Nan的歌都會唱了
那生日快樂的歌
不會太難吧
Happy birthday to you
Jordan
Happy birthday to Jordan
Ba ba ba ba ba
他們說AI有幽默感
那他真的聽得懂笑話嗎
All right
What do you call a giant pile of kittens?
I don't know
What
A meowntan
That's perfectly hilarious
在線上開會的時候
Chat
GPT AI呢
當作一個助手
聽了整個會議之後呢
他可以清楚幫你做出總結
剛開頭不是說他會算數學嗎
這數學誰不會嗎
Hmmm
但要當數學的老師
數學家教
這就不一定大家都會囉
當然啦
這展示一定要找這個
感覺很嚴格的
印度爸爸跟感覺非常非常認真
聰明的印度小孩來展示的
爸爸跟AI說
AI你不可以給小孩答案喔
你要讓他理解這整個題目
Can you first identify
which sides of the triangle
are the opposite adjacent
and hypotenuse
relative to angle alpha
All right
So I'm pretty sure this is the angle alpha right here
Right
Fict
Cart's correct
Now looking at the triangle
which side do you think is the hypotenuse
嗯
remember the hypotenuse
I'm not totally sure
I think
I think it might be this one
but I really am not sure
this side AC
you're close
actually side AC
is called the adjacent side
to the angle alpha
我已經聽不下去了
也不逼大家來聽數學啦
這是什麼數學頻道嘛
反正你就知道了
AI他現在可以用對話的方式
來教小朋友數學
教小朋友任何科目
聲音跟家教是一模模一樣一樣的
而且還超有耐心不會生氣
所以以後小朋友如果跑來問你
大人也不會的數學題
那大人再也不用承認你不會啦
好嗎
就派出Chat GPT就好了
Nice
那身為一個已經會用感情說話的機器人
看到寵物他會飆高音
會一一啊啊也是正常的
I wanna introduce you to somebody
Well hello there cutie
What's your name little sluffball
This is Bowser
Well hello Bowser
Aren't you just the most adorable little thing
視障的朋友也可以透過新版的Chat GPT
來看到世界
當然還可以請他協助來計程車
計程車的窗戶上面不是會標示說
車上還有人還是說這是空車對吧
但是看不見怎麼辦
Yes I spotted one just now
It's heading away on the left side of the road
Get ready to wave it down
跟之前的版本Chat GPT-4 Turbo相比
這一個版本的速度快了兩倍
最快可以在232毫秒的時間之內
回應這個音訊的輸入
平均反應的時間320毫秒
這就是我們兩個在講話的時候
反應時間是差不多的
開頭不是說要拿Chat GPT的反應
跟蘋果Siri來比較一下嗎
這就來了
Hey Siri
I'm gonna tell you a joke
and you tell me if it's funny ok
A few moments later
他說
你應該要跟你喜歡的人類講笑話
而不是跟他
有種悲傷的感覺
I don't know
Hey Siri
What do you call a giant pile of kittens
One eternity later
他找了這個 knowledge
就沒有幽默感
但就是找知識
最後在留言區跟大家分享一下
你聽完覺得最驚人的部分是什麼
我先來好嗎
我個人覺得
機器人有幽默感這件事情
太可怕了
謝謝你看到這裡喔
歡迎用下面的連結到LINE
跟Discord群組
跟努力的大家一起討論
我們在OKXPN派網呢
跟其他的大交易所
都幫大家爭取到了
最高8折20%OFF的交易手續費減免
用下面的連結註冊呢
你的交易成本就更低了
也歡迎告訴我
你接下來想要看什麼
我們在币圈繼續努力
下一次見拜拜